《越狱》第四季 第十一集
Prison.Break.S04E11
《越狱》  前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
"公司"要转移"锡拉"
The company is moving Scylla.
-什么时候  -明天
- When? - Tomorrow.
我搞砸了
I messed up.
-什么意思  -我提到了惠斯勒
What do you mean? I mentioned Whistler.
喂
Hello?
你就是冯
So you're Feng.
-你是Susan  -没错
Susan. That's right.
墙体用钢纤维强化过
The wall itself is fortified with steel fiber.
坏消息是  里面有重量
The bad news is that there are both weight
和扩音传感器
and microphonic sensors
一旦有任何超过
that will alert Company security
2磅的活人出现
to the presence of any breathing human being
就会拉响"公司"的安全警报
that weighs more than two pounds.
迈克
Mike.
你长了个下丘脑错构瘤
You have a hypothalamus hamartoma,
医生认为你得动手术
and the doctor feels  that you need surgery.
-再等两天  -不  明天就得做
Two days. No, tomorrow.
否则你会死的  别无选择
Otherwise, you could die, and there's no alternative.
再钻进一点点
Just a little bit more.
慢点
Go slow.
不  他绝对不值得我这么做
No, there's no way he deserves any of this.
随你说吧  美女
Sing it, sister.
他让我吃了那么多苦
After what he put me through?
我自己也不敢相信
I can hardly believe it myself.
我们必须要做的是
Look, what we must do is
你好好色诱一下他
make sure that cosmic justice rains down upon him,
一旦我们拿到将军的卡
for once we obtain the good general's card,
我们就可以轻松拿到
there ain't hardly nothing standing
冯给我们的
in between us and Mr. Feng's
1.25亿
$125 million.
我生在大山边  [好大的胸]
I was born on a mountainside.
只管拿好照相机吧
Just keep both hands on the camera.
开始吧
Let's go.
好极了
That's great.
非常感谢你  马尔登医生
Thank you so much, Dr. Malden.
你可以下午3点去见他
Yeah, he can see you today at 3:00.
-不  -我们必须去
No. We're going.
我们得有始有终
We need to finish what we started.
我们可以去办
We can do this.
我只要一天
I need one more day.
迈克尔  马尔登医生今天就能见你
Michael, Dr. Malden can see you today.
他向我们保证他不会报警
He's given us his word he won't alert the authorities.
如果你不去  你再出事的话
If you put this off and you, you collapse,
到时会是别的医生为你治疗
you're going to be treated by another doctor.
你想碰运气
Do you want to roll the dice
看其他医生会不会报警吗
that they're not going to call the cops?
还有好多事情没做
There's still so much to do.
好吧
All right.
3点
Three o'clock?
我上一次钻墙
Last time I drilled  a hole in the wall,
是在福克斯河监狱  跟迈克尔用打蛋器钻
it was with an eggbeater back in Fox River with Michael.
真不敢相信  一切就快结束了
I just can't believe it's all coming to an end,
但他却不在这里
and he's not here.
他会没事的
He'll be all right.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我不知道
I don't.
我只想让我们都集中精神
I'm just trying to keep us focused.
他病了
He's sick,
但是我确定
but I guarantee you one thing
他要是进监狱的话
that'll make him worse--
会更糟糕
going back to jail.
如果我们进不去
If we don't get in there.
我们也得进监狱
that's where we're all going.
他会没事的
He's going to be okay.
我也很害怕
I'm scared, too,
但他现在应该去医院
but a hospital's the best place for him right now.
如果没有想出计划  他是不会去的
He won't go without a plan to complete the job.
阿历克斯和费尔南多应该很快
Well, Alex and Fernando should be back soon
能带录像回来吧
with the video, right?
应该是
Should be, yeah.
那么  我们只需要第六张卡了
So, then, all we need is the sixth card.
格雷琴正在办
Gretchen's working on that.
你觉得我们能相信她吗
You really think we can trust her?
拿那张卡
To get the card?
只能这样
Absolutely.
还有呢
Anything else?
没了
Nope.
八个保安会护送"锡拉"从地下室
Eight guards will accompany Scylla from the basement bunker
移到车库  一辆装甲车会在车库待命
up to the garage, where an armored truck will be waiting.
一辆车不够保险
One truck is not going to be enough security.
所以我调了一队特工开道
That is why I have a full Secret Service escort
去马奇空军基地
to March Air Force Base.
然后把它装载入一架C-130运输机
There, it will be brought aboard a C-130.
全程需空中支援  直至抵达里弗洛克
We need air support all the way to River Rock.
里夫上校会借三架F-18给我们
Colonel Rififi is lending us three of his F-18s.
你可能觉得难以置信
It may be hard for you to believe,
但我这次确实安排妥当了
but I do have this under control.
你不用担心任何事情
There's nothing for you to worry about.
飞机着陆后  也会采取相同的警戒措施
When the plane lands, the same precautions will be taken.
装甲车
Armored truck
护送到最终地点
to guards to final location.
下午1点  老房间
Our old room.1pm.
很好
That's fine.
你要去哪
Are you going somewhere?
-我有个约会  -今天吗
I have an appointment. Today?
你告诉我不用担心任何事情
You told me there was nothing to worry about.
别告诉我是去见格雷琴
Just tell me it's not Gretchen.
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
这是我的私事
It's a personal matter.
我不想做讨论
I'm not going to discuss it.
我不相信她
I don't trust her.
也不是一天两天了
That's nothing new.
我一小时后回来
I'll be back in an hour.
有什么进展
What'd you find out?
你会一直保持清醒状态
You'll be awake the whole time.
届时  你只要做四次局部麻醉
The only anesthetic you're going to need is four minor injections of local--
两次在额头  两次在后脑
two in your forehead and two in the back of your head.
用于做支撑架
And that's for the brace?
对  支撑架
The frame, yeah, and...
安装过程是最不舒服的
attaching that is going to be the most uncomfortable part.
他们会在你颅骨上打四个固定用的钢钉
They're going to have to secure four pins into your skull
会用一个小钻子进行
and they're going to need a small drill to do it.
我们一定要听吗
Do we have to listen to this?
我想听  林肯
I want to hear this, Linc.
然后呢
And then what?
再做一次CT扫描
Uh, another CT scan.
医生会用
The doctor will use
三维成像来确定
the three-dimensional imagery to pinpoint
肿瘤的准确位置
the exact location of the growth.
确定以后呢
And once you have that?
接着就是伽玛刀治疗了
Then it's the Gamma Knife unit.
他们会给你带个头盔
They'll fit you with a helmet,
他们会确定201个洞
they'll calibrate it so that each of the 201 holes
都准确对准肿瘤位置  这时
are aimed directly for the tumor, and at that point...
车里还有两个箱子
I've got two more boxes in the car
你们得帮手拿进来
that you guys got to bring in yourself.
行了
All right.
你没事吧
You okay?
-因为上次见你时  -我很好
Because the last time I saw you... Yeah, I'm fine.
我只是有点脱水
I was just a little dehydrated.
好极了
All right, good.
这是你要的东西
This is the stuff you requested.
你确定能用这些东西进去
You sure this is gonna get you in?
我们会考虑怎么进去
Let us worry about getting in.
你还是考虑我们怎么出来吧
You worry about how we're getting out.
我已派人盯着格雷琴和巴格维尔
I got someone keeping an eye on Gretchen and Bagwell.
如果他们耍花招  他们就玩完了
If they try anything, they're getting taken out.
不会有东西阻碍我们得到"锡拉"
Nothing is going to get between us and Scylla.
你确定你没事
You sure you're all right?
没事  只不过
Yeah, it's just, uh,
我们马上要潜入公司总部
you know, we're breaking into Company headquarters,
多少会有点紧张
and, uh, you'll understand why we're all a little on edge.
明白
Understood.
我以前觉得
You know, I was thinking,
你爸找我办这事时
when your father approached me about doing this,
我感觉
I felt like I was, uh,
就像是在抓鬼一样
chasing a ghost or something, but...
但你们做的一切
'cause of the work you guys have done,
就是今天
today is the day,
我们要彻底打垮这帮混蛋
We're gonna take these bastards down.
到手了吗
You get it?
是的
Got it.
我们还剩4小时
We got four hours.
怎么说
How come?
我要去去医院治疗
I'm going in for treatment.
可以了
Here we go.
"锡拉"
Scylla.
显然  我们有很多事情要解决
Obviously, we've got a lot to figure out.
我们要穿过两面墙
We have to break through two walls.
一面水泥墙  一面玻璃墙
one concrete, one glass
还要保证不发出声音
and do it without making a sound.
高敏感抛物面扩音器
Hypersensitive parabolic microphones,
全方位扫射
pointed in all directions.
地面传感器能检测
The floor sensors can detect
附着地面两磅以上的物体
an added surface load of just two pounds.
所以
So...
我们要在不触碰地面的情况下
we have to traverse the distance between the two walls
跨过两面墙间的距离
without touching the floor
并且无论如何不能产生任何
and do all that without generating any kind
来自身体的热量
of body heat whatsoever.
因为这些是最先进的热感应器
Cause these are the latest in heat-sensing technology.
我们走错一步
We make one wrong move,
监视器就会启动  克兰兹将军就会发现我们
the camera goes on, and General Krantz will know we're inside.
不可思议
It's amazing.
所有这些安保  只有
All this security and only one man
他一个人能使用监视器
has access to video surveillance.
"公司"不想留下任何下面的记录
The Company doesn't want any record of what's going on down there.
我们能进入那个电梯吗
Can we access that elevator?
不能  电梯在"公司"大楼中间
No, it's right in the middle
那里有10层安保
of the Company building-- there are ten layers
我们要去他们看不到的地方
of security. We have to go where they're not expecting us,
先从水泥墙开始
starting with the concrete wall.
苏克雷  你在那里钻孔  对吧
Sucre, you were drilling there, right?
如你所说  墙体用钢纤维强化过
It's fortified with steel fibers, just like you said.
要穿过那面墙
All right, in order to get
需要生成一个
through that, we have to generate
电磁场
an electromagnetic field...
需要生成一个电磁场
We have to generate an electromagnetic field...
要生成
To have, uh,
符合我们需要强度的
an electromagnetic field
电磁场  我们至少
with the force that we want, we're going to need
需要两个车用电池
at least a couple of car batteries.
你能搞得到吗
Can you get that?
可以
Yeah, yeah.
我们可以办到
We can do this.
预计格雷琴什么时候
Uh, what time are we expecting Gretchen
能搞到第六张卡
to get that sixth card?
怎么这么久才来
What took you so long?
你知道我如饥似渴时会怎样
You know how I get when I'm hungry.
我要离开办公室也不容易
It wasn't easy getting away from the office.
我应该像以前那样
I could have come to you...
自己过去
like old times.
我真希望这里能有张红木桌子
I almost wish there was a mahogany desk in here.
你有点紧张
Oh... you're tense.
把外套脱了吧
Take off this jacket.
我帮你拿进去
Let me get in there.
我没有带过来
I didn't bring it with me.
我的卡
My card.
你在找这个  对吧
That is what you're looking for, right?
你在说什么呢  你的卡
What are you talking about? Your card.
你忘啦
You forget.
是我教你如何说谎的
I'm the one that taught you how to lie.
我没想到  在63岁的高龄
I never thought that, at the age of 63,
我仍然会心碎
I could still have my heart broken.
什么让你觉的有必要偷我的卡
Why did you feel you needed to steal my card?
你难道没想过稍加等待
Don't you know that if you'd waited just a little bit longer,
你也可以拥有自己的卡
you'd have had one of your own?
对不起
I'm sorry. I'm...
你要把卡卖给谁
Who are you selling it to?
不是的  不是
That's-That's not why...
谁
Who?
我是你孩子的母亲
I'm the mother of your child.
求你  看在艾米丽的份上
Please, for Emily's sake.
求你了  乔纳森
Please, Jonathan.
求求你
Please.
我爱你
I love you.
再让我看到你
If I ever see you again...
我就杀了你
I'll shoot you on sight.
有事吗  科尔
Is everything all right, Cole?
我有要事跟你说
I got something important you need to know.
我们要发财了
We're gonna be rich.
有个问题
So, here's the question.
我得花多少钱
How much is it gonna cost me
才能让你把外套脱了
to get that jacket off of you?
你说什么
Excuse me?
每次见到你
Last day I'm ever gonna see you.
你都裹得很严
You're all covered up.
我可受不了  1百美金如何
I cannot abide. $100.
你想付钱让我脱衣服
You want to pay me to take my clothes off?
不是脱光  只是脱外套
Not all of them. Just the jacket. Mm.
-2百  -我不会为你脱衣服的
$200. I'm not gonna strip for you.
可怜可怜老人家吧
Pity on an old man.
你真恶心
You're disgusting.
也很淫荡很邪恶
And lecherous and vile.
而且马上就会很有钱
And soon to be wealthy beyond belief.
1千美金
One thousand dollars.
怎么突然这么纯洁
Why so modest all of a sudden?
科尔  马上来我办公室
Cole, I need to see you in my office now.
感谢您致电伽特  有什么需要吗
Thank you for calling Gate. How can I help you?
怀特先生的顶级销售员来办公室了
It was Mr. White in his office with the lead stapler.
科尔  昨天与爱达荷的交易
Cole, yesterday, with that Idaho group,
你为公司赚了3.5万美元
you made this company $35,000.
我得有所表示
And I would like to return the favor.
这是我们的年度旅游
It's our annual cruise.
七天6夜直达环游
Seven days and six nights of non-stop pitching.
我个人通常报销5万
I personally clear $50,000 on most trips,
但凭你的功劳
but for everything you've done,
这是你应得的
it's all yours.
我的薄礼
The least I could do.
今天就出发吗
It leaves today?
回家去收拾一下
Go home and pack.
一周后见
I'll see you in a week.
不好意思  我有些事务
Unfortunately, I have some business
要在这边处理
I need to take care of right here.
它的工作原理是这样的
Okay, so, here's how it works.
一旦传感器检测到任何
As soon as the sensors pick up any kind of a heat source
90度或更高的热源  系统进入待命状态
90 degrees or more, system goes into standby,
黄灯亮起
a yellow light comes on.
待命五秒后
After five seconds in standby,
如果热源没有消失  警报拉响
if the heat source isn't gone, we have an alarm.
我们只有6秒时间穿过过道
So we got six seconds to make it across the hallway
和玻璃墙
and through the glass wall?
差不多
Basically.
如果带上液态氮
If we get our hands on some liquid nitrogen,
我们可以降低温度
we could regulate the temperature.
没错
Yeah.
一石二鸟
Kill two birds with one stone.
看能否搞到这些东西
See if you can get some of that.
我不会问你感觉如何
I'm not going to ask how you're feeling.
很好
Good.
我进"公司"四年后
About four years after I joined the bureau,
我手下第一个特工
my first special agent in charge.
被诊断患有肝癌
he was diagnosed with liver cancer.
但对他来说
But for him,
最难的不是治疗过程
the hardest part wasn't the treatment.
而是要放下工作
The hardest part was leaving the office,
当时我们正在办一起重大敲诈案
because we had this... we had this big RICO case
就要审判了
that was about to go to trial,
我们录了无数小时
and we're talking thousands
的口供  查了五年
of man hours, five years of research.
但他快要做化疗了
And the guy was going to be in chemo.
他很害怕
And he was scared.
他怕我们会输掉案子
He was scared that we were gonna lose the case,
不法之徒则会逃脱法律的制裁
and that a lot of bad men were gonna walk.
我猜  他让一群社会败类
Let me guess: He had a ragtag band of criminals
准备接受惩罚
ready to pick up the slack.
差不多
It was something like that.
我们不会让你失望的  迈克尔
We're not going to let you down, Michael.
你的上司呢
What happened to your boss?
他见证了我们的胜利
Oh, he was there to see us win.
你确定她是特工
You're sure she's a Fed?
我出1千美金  她都不脱上衣
Wouldn't take off her jacket for a thousand dollars.
她肯定收着一把枪
She's got a gun under there.
这就复杂了
It's a complication.
你这么说就对了
Well, that's a nice way to put it.
就像你没拿到第六张卡
Sort of like you not getting the sixth card.
怎么说来着  拖后腿嘛
What are we calling that now, a setback?
放松点
Relax.
你知道我放弃了什么吗
You have any idea what I'm giving up here?
我原本能拿到5万
I was guaranteed 50 grand.
就为5万哭丧着脸  你不是吧
You're crying over $50,000? Are you serious?
我有一份工作
I have a job.
我能赚钱  别人发邮件给我
I make money. I get mail.
都尊呼我  先生
People call me sir.
每天干12小时  吃着残羹剩饭
12-hour days and eating leftover lo-mein.
直觉告诉我  帝博格・巴格维尔
Something tells me Theodore Bagwell
不会坚持太长时间
wouldn't last long in this situation.
可能
Yeah, maybe,
但是科尔・普发会坚持
but Cole Pfeiffer would.
要生气  也要等明天
You want to pout, you do it tomorrow.
我们有事要办
We have work to do.
真的值1.25亿美金吗
Is it really worth $125 million?
价值是两倍
It's worth twice as much.
如果他们不交货呢
What if they refuse to hand it over?
我们要么付钱  要么杀了他们
Either we pay for Scylla, or we kill for it.
苏珊
Susan?
冯  我们得谈谈
Feng, we need to talk.
给我点时间  就一会
Hey, give me a second here, guys, just a second.
我们不能发出超过两分贝的噪音
We can't make any noise above ten decibels.
你搞了两个这家伙吗
You got two of those?
是的
Absolutely.
能成功的  对吧
This is gonna work, right?
应该会
It should.
不仅如此
No, not just that.
整个计划
The whole thing.
我们有成功的机会吗
I mean, do we even have a chance?
只要确定打洞的位置准确
Just make sure the hole is in the right place.
进展如何
So, where are we?
格雷琴没有拿到第六张卡
Gretchen didn't get us the sixth card.
我们需要那张卡  唐
We need that sixth card, Don.
我知道
I know.
如果没有那张卡
If we don't get the sixth card,
我们永远无法破解"锡拉"
We're never gonna crack Scylla.
我知道
I know it.
我们还知道什么
What else do we know?
我们知道他们今天就转移"锡拉"
Well, we know they're moving Scylla today.
我们也不能明目张胆地进将军的办公室
We know we can't just waltz into the General's office
偷最后一张卡
and steal that last card,
我们该怎么应对
so where does that leave us?
应该有办法
Then there's got to be a way.
-肯定有办法  -除非再牺牲一个人
There has to be a way. Not without losing another man.
相信我  我用一周时间思考
Believe me, I spent the last week trying to figure out
如何得到第六张卡
how to get that sixth card,
但每种方法的结果都是某人头上顶枪
And every scenario ends with a gun to someone's head,
而这是不可接受的
And that is not acceptable.
格雷琴给了一点
You know, Gretchen did pass on this one piece
信息给你
of information for you.
应该对你有帮助
This could be helpful.
喂
Hello.
买家出现了
The buyer just showed up.
好的  查清他们要干什么
All right, well, find out what they're up to.
冯先生  很高兴你能来见我们
Mr. Feng, so glad you could come and see us.
我预料我们三个
I was expecting the next time
会再聚在这个房间里
the three of us would be in the same room together,
你们会拿东西给我
that you'd have something for me.
我们预想也是如此
That was our expectation, as well,
但我们遇到点麻烦
but we've hit a few bumps in the road.
为了确保安全
Now, to ensure the item's safe recovery,
我们需要你帮忙
we need your help.
该走了
It's time to go.
逃跑是最好的办法
"All that avails is flight."
或许我爸爸查到了某些事情
Maybe my father was onto something.
如果因为我们试图搞垮公司
If they all die
他们都死了
because we tried to take down the Company,
而我还活着
and I survive because...
只是因为我因病离队
because I called in sick...
我自己该如何活下去
...how am I gonna live with myself?
你会好起来的
You're gonna get through this.
我不去医院了
I'm not going to the hospital.
什么
What?
林肯  只管上车吧
Linc, just get in the car.
我和你们一起去
I'm going with you.
如果我还有行医执照的话
If I still had a medical license,
我肯会因此吊销
I'd lose it over this.
这通常是给癫痫病人用的
This is usually given to epileptics.
它能在接下来的3小时内
It will suppress the rapid firing of neurons
抑制神经元快速发放
for the next three hours,
使病情发作的
making it unlikely
可能性变小
that you'll have a seizure in that time,
不过迈克尔  任何精神上或身体上的压力
but Michael, any added mental or physical stress...
我明白
I get it.
我说真的
I mean it.
不在万不得已的情况下  我希望你别乱动
I don't want you to move unless you absolutely have to.
等一切结束后  我就带你去医院
And as soon as this is over, I'm taking you to the hospital.
你还好吗
You all right?
一切都会按计划进行
This is gonna go exactly as planned.
我保证
I promise.
我不是在为自己祈祷
I'm not praying for me.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你要见我
You wanted to see me?
每月的第二个周二
It's the second Tuesday of the month.
你不是要参加飞鹰天使的聚餐吗
Don't you have your Eagles and Angels luncheon?
我今天不去了
I figured I'd skip it today.
你叫我来就为了确认我的午餐计划吗
You called me in here to confirm my lunch plans?
你是对的
You were right.
如果不是你的提醒  这东西就被偷了
If it weren't for you, this would be in the wind.
-她死了吗  -这样说吧
Is she dead? Let's just say
她不会再干扰我们任何人了
she won't bother either of us anymore.
但我还是想马上转移"锡拉"
But I do want Scylla moved right now.
机械师正在停机坪上检查C-130运输机
Our mechanics are on the tarmac inspecting the C-130.
确定无误后  我们就能转移了
When they sign off, we'll be ready to move.
告诉其他持卡者  在这集合
Call the other card holders, get them in here.
赛尔夫给你们打电话了吗
Did, uh, Self call you, uh, regarding
说了将军那边的小动荡吗
a little snafu with the General?
滚开
Get out of my way.
只是澄清一下
Just for, uh, clarification's sake,
第六张卡是待办的一部分  对吧  先生们
the sixth card is part of the to-do list, right, gentlemen?
游戏开始了
The game's afoot.
迈克尔有办法弄到卡吗
Does Michael have a way to get the card?
我和迈克尔・斯科菲尔德交手过
I've worked with Michael Scofield before,
不论是同伙还是敌人
both with him and against him.
如果没有完整的计划
There's no way he's going down there
他是不会动手的
without a plan to finish the job.
我接到一位老友的电话
I got a call from an old friend.
听说"锡拉"有眉目
Heard Scylla was in play.
他想知道他能否弄到手
He wants to know if he can get in on it.
竞购战
A bidding war?
他出价2百
He's prepared to offer 200.
他说真的吗
Is he for real?
我不清楚  我找了间安全的屋子
I don't know. I've set up a safe house
在那可以跟他谈  你有笔吗
where we can hear him out. Do you have a pen?
等一下
Just a minute.
皮尔蒙特街1917号
1917 Piermont.
皮尔蒙特街  记下了
Piermont,got it.
我马上过去
I'm on my way.
下午好
Uh, good afternoon.
感谢您致电伽特公司
Thank you for calling Gate.
我要去跟购买商
I got some last minute negotiations
做最后的协商
with the buyer to speak about.
我马上回来
I'll be back lickety-split.
一会见
See you later.
请稍等
Mm-hmm. Can you hold, please?
好的
All right.
就是这里
This is it.
现在  还有人
Now, does anyone have any questions
对自己要做的部分有疑问吗
about what they're supposed to do?
今早你们在墙上钻的洞
That hole you drilled in the wall this morning.
我们到了那里  如果噪音过大
once we get over there, if we make too much noise,
声波会穿过墙
the sound waves will travel through the wall
被另一侧的传感器检测到
and get picked up by the sensors on the other side.
所以从现在开始  我们要绝对安静
So, from this point on, we need absolute silence.
阿历克斯  祝好运
Alex, good luck.
你也是
You, too.
准备好了吗
You're ready?
走吧
All right.
我们要穿过两面墙
We have to break  through two walls--
一面水泥墙  一面玻璃墙
one concrete, one glass--
还要保证不发出声音
and do it without making a sound.
要穿过那面墙
In order to get through that,
需要生成一个电磁场
we have to generate an electromagnetic field.
要生成
To have
符合我们需要强度的电磁场
an electromagnetic field with the force
我们需要
that we want, we're gonna need
至少两个车用电池
at least a couple of car batteries.
先从水泥墙开始
...starting  with the concrete wall.
苏克雷  你在那里钻孔  对吧
Sucre, you were drilling there,  right?
如你所说  墙体用钢纤维强化过
It's fortified with steel fibers, just like you said.
你确定是这里吗
You sure this is it?
皮尔蒙特街1917号
1917 Piermont Avenue.
好的
Okay.
你上次查房是什么时候
When was the last time you swept a room?
在警官学院
The academy.
好的  按我的指示做
All right, just follow my lead, okay?
因为格雷琴和巴格维尔杀人不眨眼
Because Gretchen and Bagwell have no respect for human life.
-如果他们掏家伙  你就开枪  -好的
-Okay? They go for a weapon, you shoot.  -Okay.
他们想逃跑的话  开枪
They try to run, you shoot.
如果他们不束手就擒
If they do anything than kneel down and put their hands
我就开枪
behind their heads... I shoot.
别失手
And don't miss.
赛尔夫探员
Agent Self.
我们已恭候多时
We've been waiting.
是冯  他抓住他们了
That's Feng. He's got them.
斯科菲尔德和布伦斯一走出那扇门
When Scofield and Burrows walk through the door,
给他们个投降的机会
give them an opportunity to surrender.
如果能避免正面冲突  最好不过
If we can avoid confrontation, that's the best case scenario.
他们不会乖乖把东西交过来
There's no way they're gonna hand it over without a fight.
如果他们动手  我们以牙还牙
If they take that position, we'll respond in kind.
1.25亿美金
$125 million.
一个樱桃就能烂漫一整天了
Only cherry that could top this sunny day.
你可以随便处置布伦斯  马宏和苏克雷
You can keep your Burrows and your Mahone and your Sucre.
把斯科菲尔德留给我
Just leave Scofield for me.
C-130一切正常
We got a green light on the C130.
是时候了
It's time.
谢谢
Thank you.
鄂伦  塔斯宏和埃迪森随时听从安排
Oren, Tuxhorn and Edison are standing by.
斯库德里在维加斯
Scuderi was in Las Vegas.
你觉得我们能把内华达州
You think we could get the state of Nevada
变成赌城吗
to outlaw gambling?
我有些怀疑
I somehow doubt that.
他的飞机大约一小时内抵达
His plane will touch down within about an hour.
然后你就能去聚餐了
Then you can make your luncheon.
我宁愿留下
I would rather stay.
此时此刻
Now more than ever,
我们更需要法律的执行
we need the support of law enforcement.
准备好转移时
I will call you
-我会给你电话  -将军  我
when we're ready to move. General, I...
你不用担心任何事情
There's nothing more for you to worry about.
丽莎
Lisa?
做得好
Very good work.
马上派人去楼下
I need a team downstairs, now!